Speaker 1: This Christmas, millions of Americans are waking up to a tree full of presents,
Speaker 1: a secure border, an end to the war's peace on earth, you might say,
Speaker 1: a fighting chance of reigning in the federal Leviathan that has terrorized and impoverished us
Speaker 1: for two generations. We're already seeing the open the numbers. Immediately after the election,
Speaker 1: consumer sentiment jumped to its highest level since April, reversing a long stagnation under
Speaker 1: Joe Biden's handlers. Markets, of course, immediately jumped on optimism that Trump can
Speaker 1: turn the economy around like he did last time when he rekindled Obama's dying embers back into a
Speaker 1: roaring flame big enough to roast some big, beautiful chestnuts. Of course, we can't start
Speaker 1: unwrapping the presents until January 20th when Trump puts his hand on the Bible, but it has been
Speaker 1: a long time since regular Americans felt so much hope. In fact, roundabout four years to the day.
Speaker 1: This time last year, just to recollect, instead of presents, we were opening the newspapers while
Speaker 1: opening our browsers with dread, wondering what new war, what new economic calamity, what new
Speaker 1: stagflation would be unleashed upon us. Most important, millions were convinced it would never
Speaker 1: change, that they would steal every election, twist every law, pack every court until the republic was
Speaker 1: in ruins. Now, just in time for Christmas, the fear is replaced with hope. So what happened? Well, Trump,
Speaker 1: of course, is a force of nature. At age 78, he was hitting multiple campaign stops in multiple cities
Speaker 1: every day. Anything they threw at him, including bullets, only made him stronger. He attracted a
Speaker 1: crack team from Elon and Vivek to RFK and Tulsi, all dissident Democrats who could make the case
Speaker 1: to the millions of Democrat voters who are still sane. Most important for the future, the collapse of
Speaker 1: legacy media, payback for their wholesale abandonment of objectivity and truth. They pulled out every
Speaker 1: slander they could think of, yes, even the German dictator, and it bounced off. Because it turns out,
Speaker 1: if you lie enough, people stop believing. And so our colossal mainstream media has now been reduced
Speaker 1: to Don Lemon posting street interviews on YouTube while MSNBC goes to auction. This alone should give
Speaker 1: us hope for the future. Legacy media peaked. We are now the media. And sure, not only did we win,
Speaker 1: it feels like the tide has turned. So what's next? Brought to you by on chain.com. Near term, a lot of
Speaker 1: potential will be on Congress, which is struggling through a long, painful metamorphosis from a party
Speaker 1: that serves donors to a party that serves the people. But even without Congress, come January 20th,
Speaker 1: we'll be getting some very nice goodies to unwrap, including immediately releasing many of the Jan 6
Speaker 1: protesters, along with Ross Ulbricht, executive orders from the border and illegals to doge-driven
Speaker 1: deregulation and, dare we dream, federal workers unleashed to go pick fruit. But the most important is
Speaker 1: that millions of Americans have hope. They realize we can fix it, that there's light at the end of the
Speaker 1: tunnel, that it is within reach. That feeling is contagious, and it feels amazing. Okay, we'll be
Speaker 1: watching. See you next time.